#### East Rutherford, NJ 07073

□+1 (551) 206-0263 | ■ anthonyfreay@gmail.com | ♠ www.anthonyfreay.com | □ anthonyfreay | manthonyfreay

#### Summary \_

A software engineer who uses curiosity and drive to solve problems and improve technical skills. Recent internship experiences at BNY Mellon has given exposure to how an application is designed, developed, and deployed within a wide-scale enterprise environment, as well as the importance of Test-Driven Development. Always ready to learn new technologies and continually grow by pursuing technical and non-technical challenges.

### **Education** \_

Villanova University (VU)

May 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN <u>COMPUTER SCIENCE</u> & BACHELOR OF ARTS IN <u>PSYCHOLOGY</u>

Villanova, PA

Awards: O'Toole Presidential Scholar

**Current Courses:** Software Studio, Mobile App Development

Completed Courses: Data Structures & Algorithms I & II, Platform-Based Computing, Computer Systems I & II, Discrete Structures, Analysis of Algorithms, Theory of Computation, Information Visualization, Database Systems,

Software Engineering, Organization of Programming Languages, & Senior Projects

#### Skills

Intermediate: Java, HTML/CSS/JS **Programming** 

Novice: Golang, React, OpenAPI Spec (Swagger), Selenium Web Driver

Build & Deploy Novice: Maven, Docker **Databases** Novice: MongoDB, MySQL Languages English (native), Spanish (fluent)

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**BNY Mellon** Jun. 2019 - Aug. 2019

New York, NY SUMMER TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

• Overview: Develop and deploy an automated regression test of an API user interface leveraging Java and Selenium Web Driver

**BNY Mellon** Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

SUMMER TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

Jersey City, NJ

- Overview: Given freedom to fully design, develop, and deploy a full-stack URL shortening service using Golang, ReactJS, MongoDB, Nginx, and Docker company-wide, reaching 35 countries and 52,000 employees
- Front-end: Developed with a minimal design using ReactJS
- Back-end: RESTful API developed using Golang, visually documented using Swagger, and utilized MongoDB to store mapped URLs

# Leadership \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Villanova University Tech Crew (VUTC)**

Aug. 2017 - Present

SENIOR STAFF MEMBER

Villanova, PA

- · Assist in the facilitation of VU's event production needs and on-boarding new members
- In the 2018-19 academic year, produced 31 events including Orientation, Special Olympics, and Commencement

# Projects .

simple-url Redesigning and optimizing URL shortening service

Designed, developed, and deployed personal-site to improve web development skills, increase digital presence, personal-site

& improve personal branding

## Sideline

**Photography** Run & manage a freelance photography business specializing in live music, portraits, and streetscapes